{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299018076","data":{"timestamp":" 947299018076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 871c167d-d928-45f8-a91b-630bcfa23de7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299039286","data":{"timestamp":" 947299039285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKA"," userResponse":" MKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299042889","data":{"timestamp":" 947299042889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKA"," userResponse":" MKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299044437","data":{"timestamp":" 947299044437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299046811","data":{"timestamp":" 947299046811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299048366","data":{"timestamp":" 947299048366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKI"," userResponse":" MKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299051086","data":{"timestamp":" 947299051086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKI"," userResponse":" MKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299052695","data":{"timestamp":" 947299052695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKO"," userResponse":" MKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299054771","data":{"timestamp":" 947299054770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKO"," userResponse":" MKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299056340","data":{"timestamp":" 947299056339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKU"," userResponse":" MKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299059321","data":{"timestamp":" 947299059321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKU"," userResponse":" MKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299061333","data":{"timestamp":" 947299061331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299061435","data":{"timestamp":" 947299061435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 78f8e46b-618c-4e9d-aebf-5a5c4c00f18e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKU"," userResponse":" MKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299090647","data":{"timestamp":" 947299090647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKA"," userResponse":" MKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299091671","data":{"timestamp":" 947299091671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKA"," userResponse":" MKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299096032","data":{"timestamp":" 947299096031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299097076","data":{"timestamp":" 947299097075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299102066","data":{"timestamp":" 947299102066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKI"," userResponse":" MKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299103121","data":{"timestamp":" 947299103121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKI"," userResponse":" MKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299107137","data":{"timestamp":" 947299107137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKO"," userResponse":" MKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299108176","data":{"timestamp":" 947299108175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKO"," userResponse":" MKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299110794","data":{"timestamp":" 947299110794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKU"," userResponse":" MKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299111850","data":{"timestamp":" 947299111850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKU"," userResponse":" MKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299115198","data":{"timestamp":" 947299115198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299115263","data":{"timestamp":" 947299115263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 357ca7b2-75db-461e-99aa-40bf27be81d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKU"," userResponse":" MKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299144835","data":{"timestamp":" 947299144835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_she-vya-nge"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299150260","data":{"timestamp":" 947299150260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mba_mto-mba-mti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299155898","data":{"timestamp":" 947299155898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mfa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299167151","data":{"timestamp":" 947299167151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nju"," userResponse":" nju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299172272","data":{"timestamp":" 947299172272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299184019","data":{"timestamp":" 947299184018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nje"," userResponse":" nje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299189061","data":{"timestamp":" 947299189061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mza_mwi-mza-mgu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mza"," userResponse":" mza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299194018","data":{"timestamp":" 947299194018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mna-mle-kwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299199162","data":{"timestamp":" 947299199162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mwu-vyo-mna"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299204869","data":{"timestamp":" 947299204869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" mje"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299210874","data":{"timestamp":" 947299210873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299216703","data":{"timestamp":" 947299216703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" 56116a0e-1ced-4f48-ac07-3f8c63c0c833"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299248650","data":{"timestamp":" 947299248649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299249033","data":{"timestamp":" 947299249033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299249265","data":{"timestamp":" 947299249265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299249579","data":{"timestamp":" 947299249579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299249812","data":{"timestamp":" 947299249812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299253214","data":{"timestamp":" 947299253214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299253508","data":{"timestamp":" 947299253508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299254413","data":{"timestamp":" 947299254412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299254836","data":{"timestamp":" 947299254835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299257813","data":{"timestamp":" 947299257813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299258097","data":{"timestamp":" 947299258096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299258940","data":{"timestamp":" 947299258940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299259604","data":{"timestamp":" 947299259604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299260337","data":{"timestamp":" 947299260337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299260660","data":{"timestamp":" 947299260660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299260933","data":{"timestamp":" 947299260933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299261247","data":{"timestamp":" 947299261247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299261347","data":{"timestamp":" 947299261346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299261429","data":{"timestamp":" 947299261428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_053548"," gameId":" a917ddd3-750b-465c-9733-e2edd12b5da0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}